everyonedoesit.com 2019-09-25

# Privacy Policy – Everyone Does It US

## **Your Right to Privacy**

In this statement we explain how "Lifted" and "Lifted Technology Inc" respect your privacy in relation to interactions with this website and any Lifted App. When we talk about Apps we mean a Lifted application which can either be downloaded from a software application to a mobile device and can be used to access Lifted Internet Sites and/or any Lifted Services.

When we talk about "Lifted" or "us" or "we" in this statement we are referring to Lifted Technology Inc., its subsidiaries, affiliates and their respective parent and subsidiary companies.

## **Collection and Use of Information**

Information You Choose to Give Us:  We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us by phone, email or in any other way. On our website, you may request information, subscribe to our newsletter, purchase our products and services, participate in our contests and surveys, and use any other services we provide. To take advantage of these offerings, it is necessary for you to disclose personal information (referred to as “personal information,” “personally identifiable information,” and “your information”) to us, including but not limited to one or more of the following identifying information: name, age, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card details. We use the information you provide to respond to your requests, communicate with you, provide information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners, and customize and improve our services.  To purchase our goods or services, you must submit financial information in addition to certain personal information, which we use to bill you for the purchased goods or services.  

##  **Interactive Areas**

Our website and Apps will sometimes offer chat options which allow you to speak directly with a Namaste staff member while you are browsing online. Sometimes these chat options will appear automatically on your screen, they are an optional service and you can decide whether or not you wish to interact with them. This chat service is governed by the terms and conditions of use for Namaste which are available on our website and which you should read before using a chat option. It is important that when you interact with these chat options and other Interactive Areas (discussion forums, bulletin boards, blogs) you do so in a responsible way. Under no circumstances should you provide any personal or financial information when using these services. You may however choose to provide us with certain information, such as your name and contact details, if you would like us to contact you directly. If you do, we will use this information solely to respond to and deal with your comments or queries.

## **How We Keep Your Information Safe**

We know that you care about how your information is used, stored, and shared. We appreciate your trust in us to do that. To protect your information we use security measures that comply with Canadian Law and meet European Union standards. This includes computer safeguards and secure files and buildings. On Lifted’s website you will be able to read more information on how we protect your privacy and your personal data.

## **Your Right of Access**

Under the Data Protection Acts you have the right to see the personal information we hold about you.  To get a copy of this information, write to us at: Subject Access Request (SARS), Lifted Innovations, Inc., 1600 – 100 King Street West, Toronto, ON, M5X 1G5. If your information changes or you believe we have information which is inaccurate or not up-to-date please let us know and we will change it. 

## **Analytics**

Information We Collect through Google Analytics:   Users who visit this website and have javascript enabled are tracked through Google Analytics.  Google Analytics collects information anonymously and reports website trends to us without identifying individual visitors.  Google Analytics collects a variety of information from users, including  the Internet protocol (IP address) that is used to connect your computer to the Internet (which it does not report to us), your Internet service provider (ISP), browser type, type of operating system, the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our website, including date and time, cookie, the length of time you spend on particular pages, which links you click while on our site, and similar site visit information.  Google Analytics data is shared with Google. For more information about Google Analytics and information shared, visit [Google Privacy & Terms](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

## **Cookies**

This section tells you about cookies in general, how we use cookies, why we use them, and how this allows us to improve our service to you.

By using our websites and apps (through any device) you agree that this use of cookies applies to that use in addition to any other terms and conditions which may apply.

Namaste’s use of cookies may be subject to change from time to time.  Any such changes will appear here and become effective immediately. Your continued use of our websites and apps is taken as meaning that you agree to any such changes.

### What is a cookie?

Cookies are small text files that are sent to and stored on your computer, smartphone, tablet or other device for accessing the internet, whenever you visit a website or use our on-line apps.

Cookies are used to maintain the integrity of your browsing activities when you visit a website and can also be used to customise and so improve the individual customer experience.

Cookies do not in any way compromise the security of your computer. You can continue to use this website with no loss of functionality if you choose to disable cookies on your computer. However, use of Namaste websites and applications requires cookies to be enabled in order for our services to function securely and correctly.

More general information on cookies can be found on aboutcookies.org. This includes information on how to disable cookies.

Guidelines from the Office of the Data Protection Commissioner for the contents and use of Privacy Statements on websites, including expected standards for cookies can be found on http://www.dataprotection.ie/docs/PrivStatements/290.htm

### How we use Cookies

Namaste uses cookies to monitor our website traffic, to ensure better service levels, and to enable us provide you with additional features such as customised delivery of service to you.

To achieve this, there are different types of cookies in use. They all work in the same way, but have minor differences which are explained below.

### Session Cookies

Session cookies last only for the duration of your visit and are deleted when you close your browser. They are essential for secure user navigation through the site and enable the delivery of basic functionality.

Specifically they ensure the security and integrity of your session, preventing fraudulent use and keeping you signed in while you move between pages and service your account.

### Persistent Cookies

Persistent cookies last after you have closed your browser, and allow us to remember your actions and website preferences.

Namaste uses persistent cookies to analyse customer visits to our sites. These cookies help us to understand how customers arrive at and use our sites so we can improve the overall Namaste on-line experience.

### Analytics Cookies

Finally, we use analytics cookies to help us make our websites even better for those who visit them regularly. This type of cookie helps us to further understand how individual visitors use our on-line services and allows us to improve the overall service and products offered to you.

## **Disclaimer**

This Site and our Apps may contain hypertext links to associated web sites maintained by Lifted and you are warned that when you enter such sites, you will be subject to the terms and conditions of those sites. There may also be links to web sites not maintained by Lifted and you are warned that when you enter other websites via such hypertext links, you will not be subject to the terms and conditions of Lifted and you will not benefit from the protections afforded to you in using our Site. Lifted will not be liable in any way for the content, availability, or use of such third party websites and you use such links entirely at your own risk.

## **Additional Information**

Lifted partners with third parties who provide services to us. You can navigate to these parties’ websites from our website. Our partners may use cookies, and you can find out more on their website.

## **Amendments**

Lifted reserves the right in its sole discretion to amend this privacy statement at any time, you should regularly check this privacy statement for any amendments.

## **Terms and Conditions**

This Privacy Statement is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Lifted Innovations, Inc. website, a copy of these is available on www.namastetechnologies.com. It is important that you read the terms and conditions of use as where there is a conflict between this Privacy Statement and the Terms and Conditions of Use, the Terms and Conditions of Use shall prevail.

By accessing and continuing to navigate this website or by downloading and using our Apps you acknowledge and agree to the processing of your personal data in the manner outlined above. You also agree that in certain circumstances we may be obliged to disclose personal information relating to you to third parties in order to prevent, detect or prevent fraud.

Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
